// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following contains all life on earth?",
    answer: "A. Biosphere",
    options: [
      "A. Biosphere",
      "B. Community",
      "C. Earth",
      "D. Ecosystem",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following refers to a chemical structure consisting of two or more atoms?",
    answer: "C. Molecule",
    options: [
      "A. Atomic number",
      "B. Mixture",
      "C. Molecule",
      "D. Solution",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the fundamental unit of structure and function among organisms?",
    answer: "A. Cell",
    options: [
      "A. Cell",
      "B. Organ",
      "C. Organ system",
      "D. Tissue",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the type of cell that lacks a true nucleus and membrane-bound organelles?",
    answer: "C. Prokaryotic",
    options: [
      "A. Eukaryotic",
      "B. Muscle cell",
      "C. Prokaryotic",
      "D. Sex cell",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the form of the genetic materials that take in chromosomes?",
    answer: "B. DNA",
    options: [
      "A. Chromatid",
      "B. DNA",
      "C. Gene",
      "D. RNA",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the entire collection of genetic instruction that an organism inherits?",
    answer: "C. Genomes",
    options: [
      "A. Alleles",
      "B. Gene expressions",
      "C. Genomes",
      "D. Genomics",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Producers in a food chain or web are _______ in nature.",
    answer: "B. Photosynthetic",
    options: [
      "A. Heterotrophic",
      "B. Photosynthetic",
      "C. Single-celled",
      "D. Singular",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is the father of evolution?",
    answer: "B. Charles Darwin",
    options: [
      "A. Alexander Graham Bell",
      "B. Charles Darwin",
      "C. Copernicus",
      "D. Gregor Mendel",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the ideal duration of pregnancy among humans?",
    answer: "D. 38 weeks",
    options: [
      "A. 32 weeks",
      "B. 34 weeks",
      "C. 36 weeks",
      "D. 38 weeks",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is considered as an incomplete form of sexual reproduction?",
    answer: "C. Hermaphroditism",
    options: [
      "A. Budding",
      "B. Fragmentation",
      "C. Hermaphroditism",
      "D. Parthenogenesis",
    ],
  },
];
